RTOBJDDSKINRSK
performance real time object
detection by SK in flask
object
detector.
... open
folder
Is he spelling on to a model?
He has a can't take
a repository clone to Sakti. He
enough for a very
easy&#44; easy.
Activate.
Virtually
... Virtually ...
./benv/scripts/scrtls
Activate over here ... ...
you know main easy.payu and import
the name from the dash
main function define cry this main name
model as yo local or en
en for nano dot pt extension is download
is Chrome model going up import for Fill
cap function is memory cv2 see video
camera video capture video capture is a
function say video capture 00
camera
01&#44; 2&#44;
3&#44; if not cap&#44; open a camera
error. The white&#44; white&#44;
true. Red frame
is good. Frame
function. Red
function. If not&#44; read
to fail break
program.
Result is going to model frame to result
model capacity frame model
capacity. Result functions defined
annotated frame.
... ...
CV to ensure YOLO V8 object
detection...
uh annotated frame uh there you go
uh it seems you you know
CV to ensure the split annotated frame
window title annotated from window frame
and what's the title
exit condition of exit cable exit key
condition the CV2
CV2 wait one one millisecond
initial
computer different
operating systems
Sandbox bar&#44; it is bad of text here
though&#44; is me error ID&#44; this
layer here.
Cap.release&#44; destroy builder&#44;
just see how much you can get to
cap.release. Webcam go
applications&#44; sorry windows.
Last wall&#44; if name if underscore name
underscore is equals to is equals to main
underscore main underscore main file&#44;
main function. ... ...
yeah
100% CPU ......................
Mira ye wala ye yellow model I scanner be
a man I say value file when I clean it is
came there be model dehira a dot pt se
bada wala and the key so mb super model
able downloaded scanner the way the
balance and download is like yeah that
game is cover cartoon was good fire we
will not sign now is them neighbor
children when I see you
many others it's good get up at all with
me that he has any
what's your word valid find it all ?
this repo is made
for explaining
in... Zulo
model ... ...
README file ...
.........................
I will make a platform on
github using YOLO
model to make
real time
detection make a
see looking
readme
file for that
which even
contain
everything
like the
yeah tip
commands to download etc.
make that in markdown
here here is
the link of repo
that and gave
me a come here
.............................................
for this.
This may be new file in this particular
area.
Here we have the new detection here&#44;
this program and we can features
installation
Requirement.txt.
python python is very
nice living python
only have parabiskit umm
... ... ... ...
... But yeah&#44;
to
explore... Save...
Installation...
................
Pip
command to install
then is
... ...
you know License .
License .
Hello yeah I'm ready to review
and submit.
License
.................................................